[Guest] 未宣而战早已司空见惯。可悲的是，我们的政府发动预防性战争，也就是所谓的侵略，而美国民众对此却毫无怨言。令人遗憾的是，
Undeclared wars are commonplace. Tragically, our government engages in preemptive war, otherwise known as aggression, with no complaints from the American people. Sadly,
[Guest] 我们已经习惯了政府以不正当方式使用武力。要建立一个真正自由的社会，就必须理解并拒绝主动使用武力这个问题。
we have become accustomed to living with the illegitimate use of force by government. To develop a truly free society, the issue of initiating force must be understood and rejected.
[Guest] 如果有时候，爱你的国家就意味着你必须改革甚至废除政府呢？如果 Jefferson 是对的呢？如果最好的政府就是管得最少的政府呢？
What if sometimes, to love your country, you had to alter or abolish the government? What if Jefferson was right? What if that government is best which governs least?
[Guest] 如果当政府错了的时候，正确反而会变得危险呢？如果为自由而战、哪怕牺牲，也比像奴隶一样活着更好呢？如果自由面临的最大危险时刻就是现在呢？
What if it is dangerous to be right when the government is wrong? What if it is better to perish fighting for freedom than to live as a slave? What if freedom's greatest hour of danger is now?
[Host] 大家好，我是 Andrew Napolitano 法官，欢迎来到 Judging Freedom。今天是 2026 年 4 月 14 日，星期二。John Mearsheimer 教授马上就到，来聊聊 Netanyahu 一伙人究竟是怎么把总统给骗了。
Hi, everyone. Judge Andrew Napolitano here for Judging Freedom. Today is Tuesday, April 14th, 2026. Professor John Mearsheimer will be with us in just a moment on just how did Netanyahu and company trick the president.
[Host] 不过先看这个。
But first this.
[Host] 当别人说“我早就告诉过你了”的时候，你是不是也会尴尬得直起鸡皮疙瘩？抱歉，我早就告诉过你，黄金和白银会因为过度印钞、通胀和全球不确定性而大幅受益。现在来了，已经发生了。黄金和白银都创下了历史新高。
Don't you just cringe when people say, I told you so? Sorry. I told you gold and silver would reap the benefits due to excessive money printing, inflation, and global uncertainty. It's here. It's happened. Gold and silver reached all-time highs.
[Host] 你给 Lear Capital 打电话买一些了吗？现在还不晚。专家预测接下来价格还会更高。为什么？因为什么都没变。地缘政治混乱、生活成本危机以及美元走弱，正推动各国央行增加黄金储备。
Did you call Lear Capital and buy some? It's not too late. Experts are predicting higher prices ahead. Why? Nothing has changed. Geopolitical chaos, cost of living crises and a weaker dollar are driving central banks to boost their gold reserves.
[Host] 预测显示，黄金可能涨到每盎司 6000 美元，白银可能涨到每盎司 200 美元。就连 Morgan Stanley 都放弃了 60 比 40 的配置规则，改成了 60-20-20，把 20% 配到贵金属上。他们已经开始补课了，你也该这样。给业内最顶尖的人打电话吧。
Forecast suggests gold could hit $6,000 an ounce and silver $200 an ounce. Even Morgan Stanley ditched the 60-40 rule for 60-20-20, putting 20% into precious metals. They're getting educated, and you should too. Call the best in the business.
[Host] 也就是我信任的那帮人，Lear Capital。拿他们的报告，了解事实，买点黄金和白银。告诉他们是法官介绍你来的，最高可拿到价值 2 万美元的额外黄金或白银奖励。拨打 800-511-4620，或者访问 leargujudnap.com。
As in the people I trust, Lear Capital. Get their reports, get the facts, get some gold and silver. Tell them the judge sent you and get up to $20,000 in bonus gold or silver. Call 800-511-4620 or go to leargujudnap.com.
[Host] Professor Mehrshammer，欢迎你来，我亲爱的朋友。感谢你一如既往地体谅我的时间安排，总是这么客气。在我们谈到……到底是不是，以及当然还有是否……之前，
Professor Mehrshammer, welcome here, my dear friend. Thank you for accommodating my schedule as you always so graciously do. Before we get into... Whether or not, and certainly whether,
[Host] 以色列人骗了 President Trump，让他相信这场战争 96 小时内就会结束，我想先问你几个关于最近事态的问题。
the Israelis tricked President Trump into believing this war would be over in 96 hours, I want to ask you a few questions about more recent events.
[Host] 上周末在 Islamabad 发生的那些事，是真正以达成长期和平为目标的谈判吗？
Were the events in Islamabad this past weekend a true negotiation intended to produce a long-term peace?
[Guest] 看起来绝对不像。我想说两点。
It sure doesn't look like that. I mean, I'd make two points.
[Guest] 第一，看起来美国人几乎完全认为自己掌握着主动权，可以在核问题上对伊朗人发号施令、强加条件。而且如果你看看我们当时提出的要求，
One is it appears that the Americans thought they were in the driver's seat almost completely and could dictate terms on the nuclear issue to the Iranians. And if you look at what we were demanding,
[Guest] 很难相信那是一个认真的谈判立场，是我们真正拿出来谈的条件。伊朗人早就明确表示，他们绝不会彻底放弃自己的铀浓缩能力，就这么简单。
it's hard to believe that this was a serious negotiating position that we were. We were putting forward. The Iranians have long made it clear they're not going to completely give up their nuclear enrichment capability, period.
[Guest] 事情就是这样。而且在我们根本没打赢这场战争的情况下，还想强迫他们这么做，这完全说不通。我要说的第二点，我觉得这是非常重要的一点。
End of story. And the idea that we were going to force them to do it when we're not winning the war makes no sense. Second point I'd make, and this is, I think, a very important point.
[Guest] 如果想通过某种谈判协议，以有意义的方式结束这场冲突，就必须处理一大堆问题。核问题只是其中之一。而我看不到任何证据表明其他那些问题被拿出来处理了。
To get any form of negotiated agreement that puts an end to this conflict in a meaningful way. You have to deal with a whole host of issues. The nuclear issue is just one of them. And I don't see any evidence that those other issues were addressed.
[Guest] 这里面包括赔偿问题、长期来看由谁控制这条海峡、Hezbollah 和 Israel 的问题怎么处理、对 Iran 的制裁怎么办，还有美国在该地区的军事基地会怎样。
And this involves things like reparations, who controls the strait for the long term, what happens with Hezbollah and Israel, what happens with sanctions on Iran, what happens with American military. curry bases in the region.
[Guest] 这些都是 Iran 或美国摆上谈判桌的问题。但我看不到任何证据表明这些问题被讨论过。看起来一切都围着核问题在转。
These are all issues that either the Iranians or the Americans have put on the table. And I don't see any evidence that they were discussed. It looks like everything revolved around the nuclear issue.
[Guest] 而且就连在这个问题上，他们也才刚起步，更别说取得实质进展了。所以我也不确定这最终会把我们带到哪里。
And even there, they couldn't get out of the batter's box, but less to first base. So I'm not sure where this all leaves us.
[Host] 所以，当时是 Iran 的议长和外长在谈判，而对方是那个国家的副总统——这个国家刚刚派出几百架飞机和几百名士兵，试图去偷走浓缩铀。
So you have the Speaker of the Parliament and the Foreign Minister of Iran negotiating with the He was the vice president of the country that had just dispatched a few hundred.
[Host] 当然，那次偷窃行动失败了，因为其中一架飞机坠毁了，他们最后不得不把行动变成一次救援任务。还有，参与谈判的另外两个人，Iran 人明确说过不要带他们来。
their planes and a few hundred troops to try and steal the enriched uranium and of course that attempted theft failed when one of the planes crashed and they had to turn it into a rescue mission you also had presence of the negotiation two people that the Iranians said don't bring them
[Host] 别带 Litkov 和 Kushner 来，因为我们不信任他们。他们已经骗了我们两次，一次是在 6 月，一次是在 2 月，让我们以为谈判正在进行，实际上你们却在策划袭击。
Don't bring Litkov and Kushner because we don't trust them. They duped us twice, both in June and in February, leading us to believe negotiations were going on while you were planning an attack.
[Host] Kushner 和 Kushner 会不会作为以色列安插在 Vance 身边的耳目出现？你怎么看？
Would Kushner and Kushner show up as the Israeli eyes and ears on Vance? What do you think?
[Guest] 嗯，我觉得非常重要的一点是，你得明白，之所以你——
Well, I think it's very important to understand that the reason you are.
[Guest] 几乎不可能达成任何有实质意义的协议、把整个问题彻底了结，是因为在美国怎么跟伊朗谈判这件事上，以色列掌握着方向盘，而且以色列坚定地致力于至少在 Tehran 实现政权更迭，扶植一个会向以色列和美国低头的政权。
highly unlikely to ever get any form of meaningful agreement and put this whole problem to bed is because the Israelis are in the driver's seat when it comes to how the Americans negotiate with the Iranians and the Israelis are firmly committed to at least achieving regime change in Tehran and getting a regime that will surrender.
[Guest] 或者他们真正想做的，其实是摧毁 Iran。所以，考虑到以色列的议程，再考虑到以色列对美国拥有的巨大影响力，你怎么可能解决这场冲突呢？
Israel and the United States in place or What they'd really like to do is wreck Iran. So given Israel's agenda and given the tremendous leverage that Israel has over the United States, how do you ever solve this conflict?
[Guest] 以色列人绝不会同意让 Iran 处在这样一种状态：经济可以增长，同时还保有铀浓缩能力和相关设备能力。他们就是不会接受这一点。他们会继续在 Iran 问题上制造麻烦。
The Israelis are not going to agree to leave Iran in a position where it can grow economically and it still maintains its enrichment. equipment capability. They simply won't accept that. They'll continue to cause trouble vis-a-vis Iran.
[Guest] 而且由于游说集团的力量，我们也会跟着走。顺便说一句，正如你指出的那样，你在 Islamabad 已经看到了以色列的影响力。我的意思是，不光有两个以色列代理人站在 Vance 身后、盯着他的一举一动，
And because of the power of the lobby, we'll go along. And by the way, you saw Israel's influence, as you pointed out, in Islamabad. I mean, not only did you have two Israeli assets standing behind Vance and looking over his shoulder,
[Guest] 而且很明显，Vance 在谈判期间实际上还给 Netanyahu 打过一次电话，并且他一直和 Trump 以及 Rubio 保持密切联系，而这两个人显然也都在和以色列方面保持联系。除此之外，
but it's quite clear that Vance actually called Netanyahu once during the negotiations, and he was in constant contact with Trump and with Rubio, both of whom sure were in contact with the Israelis. And on top of all that.
[Guest] 副总统 Vance 想当美国总统。他想赢下 2028 年的大选，Marco Rubio 也是一样。这就说明，Vance 和 Rubio 都会跟着以色列的调子起舞。所以问题就在于，
Vice President Vance wants to be the president of the United States. He wants to win the 2028 election, as does Marco Rubio. And that tells you that both Vance and Rubio will dance to Israel's tune. So the question is,
[Guest] 那从美国的角度看，你到底要怎么拼凑出一个谈判立场，才能和 Iran 达成某种真正有意义的协议？答案是，我觉得做不到。
how do you ever put together a negotiating position, talking from an American perspective, where you can get some sort of meaningful agreement? with Iran and the answer is I don't think you can
[Host] Vance 在政治上已经掉进这么大一个坑里了，他到底怎么可能爬得出来？我的意思是，他名义上是去谈停火，可这场战争他一直反对到最后一刻。而且就在那之前，他刚刚结束了三天的竞选活动。
How can Vance possibly dig himself out of the hole that he's already in politically? I mean, he's there ostensibly to negotiate the ceasefire of a war that he opposed right up until the last minute. He had just finished three days of campaigning.
[Host] 他还在替 Viktor Orban 向匈牙利民众拉票，而 Orban 刚刚遭遇了一场压倒性的惨败。他在 21 个小时里和 President Trump 通了 11 次电话，这就说明，他显然根本没有任何权限拍板任何事情，所有事都得先请示 Trump。当然，这里我要借用 Prime Minister Netanyahu 的说法。
English to Hungarian people for Viktor Orban who suffered a resounding overwhelming defeat and he talks to President Trump 11 times in 21 hours meaning he obviously had no authority whatsoever to agree on anything without running everything past Trump and then of course I'm going to use Prime Minister Netanyahu's word
[Host] 他是在向以色列总理汇报。Chris，第三点。
He reported to the Israeli Prime Minister Chris number three
[Host] 我昨天和副总统 J.D. Vance 通了话。
I spoke yesterday with Vice President J.D. Vance.
[Host] 他是在从 Washington 回程的飞机上给我打的电话。
He called me from his plane on the way back from Washington.
[Host] 他向我详细汇报了谈判进展，就像本届政府的人每天都会做的那样。
He reported to me in detail, as the people of this administration do every day, on the development of the negotiations.
[Host] 这一次，谈判的破裂——这次破裂是美方造成的，因为美方不愿容忍 Iran 公然违反了进入谈判的协议。说白了，
In this case, the explosion in the negotiations-the explosion came from the American side, which was not willing to tolerate the blatant violation of the agreement to enter negotiations by Iran. Essentially,
[Host] 当时达成的协议是先停火，然后 Iran 立即开放过境口岸。但他们没有这么做。美国人也不愿意接受。
the agreement was that there would be a ceasefire and Iran would immediately open the crossings. They didn't do that. The Americans were not willing to accept it.
[Host] 他还向我传达说，从 Trump 总统和美国的角度来看，摆在桌面上的核心问题，是清除所有浓缩材料，并确保未来几年内不再进行任何浓缩活动，
He also conveyed to me that the central issue on the table from the perspective of President Trump and the United States is the removal of all enriched material and ensuring that there is no more enrichment in the coming years,
[Host] 而且这可能会持续几十年。
and this could be for decades.
[Host] 嗯，他向我详细汇报了一个关键词和一句很耐人寻味的话，这也是这个政府里的人每天都会做的事——向他汇报。这个让你意外吗？
Well, one key word and one fascinating phrase he reported to me in detail as the people of of this administration do every day. Report to him. Does this surprise you?
[Guest] 不，这只是进一步证明了我几分钟前说的话。Israel 基本上把我们拿捏住了。
No, this is just more evidence for what I said a few minutes ago. The Israelis basically own us.
[Guest] 他们在很大程度上主导了我们和 Iranians 谈判时的立场。所以我才跟你说，当 Israelis 一心想要摧毁 Iran，并确保 Iran 完全不具备任何核能力时，我们到底要怎么解决这场冲突？
They're largely driving our negotiating position with the Iranians. And this is why I said to you, how do we ever resolve this conflict when the Israelis are committed to wrecking Iran and making sure Iran has no nuclear capability at all?
[Guest] 答案就是，你根本没法以任何有意义的方式解决这件事。这场冲突还会没完没了地持续下去。
And the answer is there's no way you can resolve this in some meaningful way. This conflict is going to go on and on and on.
[Guest] 会一直持续下去，因为 Israelis 就是想让它没完没了地继续，而我们又没有能力对 Israelis 说不，就这么简单。
on because the Israelis wanted to go on and on and on and we are not in a position to stand up to the Israelis it's as simple as that
[Host] 所以，当总统面对自己情报机构提供的情报，基本都在说这场仗不可能轻松打赢；而某个外国情报机构却说，别担心，96小时内就结束了，
So when the president is confronted with intelligence from his own intelligence agencies that basically say this is not going to be an easy war to win. And a foreign intelligence agency, so don't worry about it, it'll be over within 96 hours,
[Host] 我们会干掉 Ayatollah，我们会煽动街头骚乱，暴徒会接管政府。你听说过有哪位美国总统会拒绝本国情报机构的情报，转而接受外国机构的吗？我说的，
we'll kill the Ayatollah, we'll foment riots in the streets, the rioters will take over the government. Have you ever heard of an American president rejecting the intel of his own agencies and accepting that of a foreign entity? I'm speaking,
[Host] 当然，就是 Mossad。
of course, of Mossad.
[Guest] 没有，我觉得 Trump 和 Netanyahu 的这些会面，以及 Trump 和他顾问们之间的讨论，真的相当不寻常。不寻常就不寻常在于，他所有的核心顾问——你也许会想用“deep state”这个词——
No, I think what happened in these meetings between Trump and Netanyahu and Trump and his advisors is really quite extraordinary. And it's extraordinary in the sense that all his principal advisors, you might want to use the word the deep state.
[Guest] 他们全都在亮橙灯，甚至可以说是红灯，告诉他攻击 Iran 不是个好主意。
They all were flashing orange lights, if not red lights, and telling him that attacking Iran was not a good idea.
[Host] 除了 Pistol Pete。
Except for Pistol Pete.
[Guest] 对，除了 Pistol Pete，不过他几乎都不算数，因为大家都明白，他其实并不是个严肃的思考者。我相信 President Trump 到了这个时候自己也意识到了这一点，
Yeah, except for Pistol Pete, but he almost doesn't count because everybody understands he's really not a serious thinker. I'm sure that President Trump even realizes that at this point in time,
[Guest] 但除了他之外，其他所有人都一样，包括 John Ratcliffe，Ratcliffe，按
but except for him, all the other people, including John Ratcliffe, Ratcliffe, according
[Host] 对。
Yes.
[Guest] 根据报道，
to reports,
[Guest] John Ratcliffe 非常亲以色列，但作为 CIA 的负责人，他毫无疑问和各种分析师都谈过，而那些分析师当时告诉他，这主意简直荒唐透顶。但推动这件事的是以色列方面，也就是 David Barnea，他是……的负责人
and John Ratcliffe is super pro-Israel, but as the head of the CIA, he was undoubtedly talking to all sorts of his analysts who were telling him that this was a cockamamie idea. But it was the Israelis in the form of David Barnea, who was the head of...
[Guest] 他是 Mossad 的负责人，还有总理 Netanyahu，基本上是他们把总统 Trump 给忽悠了，让他以为自己能迅速而决定性地取胜。不过再说一遍，
who is the head of Mossad and Prime Minister Netanyahu, who basically bamboozled President Trump into thinking that he could win a quick and decisive victory. But again,
[Guest] 这里真正值得注意的是，他的主要顾问当时都在告诉他，这是个馊主意，他会把自己拖进一大堆麻烦里，而事情也的确就是这么发展的。
what's really remarkable about this is that his principal advisors were telling him this is a bad idea and that he was going to get himself into a well of a lot of trouble, which is exactly what has happened.
[Host] 嗯，是以色列人把他拖进了这场战争。那他们会把他弄出来吗？不会。
Well, the Israelis got him into the war. Are they going to get him out? No.
[Guest] 不会，他们只会让他继续陷在里面。这
No, they're going to keep them in. That's
[Host] 对。
Right.
[Guest] 我想跟你说的是，你得明白，大家都在谈我们要怎么跟伊朗人谈判，伊朗人和美国人能不能在这件事上达成协议。
my point to you. You have to understand that, you know, everybody's talking about how we're going to negotiate with the Iranians and can the Iranians and the Americans work out a deal here.
[Guest] 但这其实都不是重点，因为事实是，以色列人根本对达成协议没兴趣。记得吗，就在 Trump 总统宣布停火之后，马上发生了什么。
That's, you know, all beside the point because the fact is the Israelis have no interest in a deal. Remember what happened right after President Trump announced there was a ceasefire.
[Guest] 以色列猛烈轰炸了 Lebanon。他们以极其凶狠的方式袭击了 Lebanon，杀害了大量 Lebanon 的无辜平民，目的就是要破坏停火。
The Israelis slammed Lebanon. They attacked Lebanon in a ferocious way. They murdered huge numbers of innocent civilians in Lebanon, all for the purposes of undermining the ceasefire,
[Guest] 因为按照 Trump 总统以及更广义上的 Trump 政府所同意的停火协议，以色列必须停止攻击 Hezbollah。这一点是伊朗人坚持要求的。停火期间，以色列不能攻击 Hezbollah。
because the ceasefire, as was agreed to by President Trump and the Trump administration more generally, call for Israel to stop attacking Hezbollah. The Iranians insisted on this. Israel cannot attack Hezbollah during the ceasefire.
[Guest] 当然，当 Trump 打电话给 Netanyahu，告诉他这是停火中的一项主要条款时，Netanyahu 很明确地表示他不同意。
And of course, when Trump called up Netanyahu and told him that was one of the principal provisions in the ceasefire, Netanyahu made it clear he did not agree.
[Guest] 然后他就出去开始轰炸 Lebanon，很大程度上就是为了破坏停火，因为以色列人不想停火。他们想让战争继续打下去。他们想让我们摧毁 Iran，或者推动政权更迭，
And then he went out and he started bombing Lebanon in large part to undermine the ceasefire because the Israelis don't want a ceasefire. They want the war to go on. They want us to destroy Iran or to produce regime change,
[Guest] 而这两件事都没有发生，也不会发生，这样一来就只剩下一个选项：为了让以色列人满意，摧毁 Iran。
which has not happened and is not going to happen, which leaves us with one option, destroying Iran to make the Israelis happy.
[Host] 那这周结束时，所谓停火的这两周到期之后，会发生什么？
So what happens at the end of this week when the two weeks of the so-called ceasefire are over?
[Host] Trump 会恢复轰炸，还是会等他这场“封锁中的封锁”见分晓？他脑子里到底在想什么？抱歉啊，Professor，我一口气问了三个问题。偏偏还是在复活节星期天，发了那么一条极其粗俗、极不合时宜的推文。
Does Trump resume bombing or does he await the outcome of his blockade of the blockade? Well, what's going on in his mind? I'm sorry for the triple questions here, Professor. An Easter Sunday in a very profane and most inappropriate tweet.
[Host] 要求 Hormuz Strait 保持开放，现在他自己却把它封锁了。
demanding the Strait of Hormuz be open, now he's blockading it.
[Guest] 现在的情况是，他已经慌了。我的意思是，他现在明白，发动这场战争是个天大的失误。要是能回到 2 月 27 日，知道后来会发生这些事的话，他就不会攻击 Iran。
Well, what's going on is that he's desperate. I mean, he understands at this point that he made a colossal blunder starting this war. If we could go back to February 27th, he would not attack Iran knowing what has happened.
[Guest] 现在的问题是，他怎么才能让自己脱离这个局面？而他面临的麻烦在于，Iranians 是非常难对付的对手。他们手里有很多牌可打。另一边，他还得应付 Israelis，
And the question now is, how does he get himself out of this situation? And the problem he faces is that the Iranians are a formidable adversary. They have lots of cards to play. And on the other side, he's dealing with the Israelis,
[Guest] 他们同样是非常难对付的对手，我这里是很谨慎地在措辞。Israelis 是 United States 的一个强劲对手，而且他们手里有非常有力的牌可打，因为他们有一个叫 Israel lobby 的体系，
who are a formidable adversary, and I'm choosing my words carefully here. The Israelis are a formidable adversary of the United States, and they have very powerful cards to play because they have this institution called the Israel lobby,
[Guest] 它由 United States 各种各样的机构和个人组成，权力极大，而且会不遗余力地确保 U.S. 的外交政策跟着 Israel 的调子走。所以 Trump 现在是进退两难。
comprised of all sorts of institutions and individuals in the United States who have enormous power and go to great lengths to make sure that U.S. U.S. foreign policy dances to Israel's tune. So Trump is caught between a rock and a hard place.
[Guest] 一边是 Israelis，另一边是 Iranians，而他几乎没有任何谈判空间。
He's got the Israelis on one side and the Iranians on the other side, and he has hardly any negotiating room.
[Host] Netanyahu 在 Beirut 市中心商业区屠杀平民，到底达成了什么？平民啊。
What has Netanyahu accomplished by slaughtering civilians in a shopping area in downtown Beirut? Civilians.
[Guest] 嗯，我觉得他面临的问题，其实和 Iran 无关。问题在于，他在对付 Hezbollah 这件事上表现得很差。你要记得，在 2023 年和 2024 年那几年，
Well, I think the problem that he faces, this is independent of Iran. is that he is doing very poorly against Hezbollah. You want to remember in the years 2023 and 2024,
[Guest] 当时看起来，以色列已经把 Hezbollah 打得元气大伤，几乎等于被拔了牙。后来，2 月 28 日对 Iran 的战争爆发，Hezbollah 也加入进来，帮助他们的伊朗盟友。
it looked like the Israelis had decimated Hezbollah to the point where it was effectively defanged. And then the war against Iran started on February 28th and Hezbollah joined in to help its Iranian allies.
[Guest] 而且很值得注意的是，Hezbollah 在两个方面都非常有效。一个是向以色列北部、甚至 Tel Aviv，大规模发射火箭弹和导弹。
And it's been quite remarkable how effective Hezbollah is in two different ways, one at lobbying rockets and missiles in large numbers at northern Israel and even into Tel Aviv.
[Guest] 很明显，就火箭弹和导弹力量而言，Hezbollah 并没有被拔掉牙。但除此之外，如果你看看黎巴嫩南部正在发生的战斗，你要记得，以色列人一直想
It's quite clear that Hezbollah in terms of its rocket and missile force has not been defanged. But furthermore, if you look at the battles that have been taking place in southern Lebanon, you want to remember the Israelis are interested.
[Guest] 拿下黎巴嫩南部，一直到 Litani River。可实际上，在黎巴嫩南部的坦克战和步兵战里，以色列确实被 Hezbollah 打得很惨。
interested in conquering southern Lebanon up to the Latani River. The Israelis have really been clobbered by Hezbollah in the, you know, the tank battles and the infantry battles in southern Lebanon.
[Guest] 而且以色列人实际上已经后撤了，他们也不再谈什么把黎巴嫩南部殖民到 Litani River 一线。现在他们控制的，只是以色列北部
And the Israelis have actually pulled back and they're no longer talking about colonizing southern Lebanon up to the Latani River. They now have a very narrow strip that they control along the border between northern Israel.
[Guest] 和黎巴嫩南部边境沿线的一小条狭长地带。所以 Hezbollah 依然活得好好的、战力也还在。而我认为 Netanyahu 想做的是，在黎巴嫩煽动一场内战。
Israel and southern Lebanon. So Hezbollah is alive and well. And what I think Netanyahu wants to do is he wants to foment a civil war in Lebanon.
[Guest] 他想挑起一场战争，一边是政府，另一边是 Hezbollah，以此来削弱 Hezbollah，也借此削弱黎巴嫩。
He wants to foment a war between the government on one side and Hezbollah on the other as a way of weakening Hezbollah and as a way of weakening Lebanon.
[Host] 这就能解释他为什么提出要谈判了，不是跟 Hezbollah 谈，而是跟黎巴嫩政府谈。
That would explain his offer to negotiate, not with Hezbollah, but with the government of Lebanon.
[Guest] 完全没错。而且以色列媒体上有各种说法，说以色列人真正想做的，是让黎巴嫩政府去解除 Hezbollah 的武装，因为以色列人自己没法解除 Hezbollah 的武装，正如我刚才说的。
Absolutely. And there's all sorts of talk in the Israeli press that what the Israelis are interested in doing is getting the Lebanese government to disarm Hezbollah because the Israelis can't disarm Hezbollah, as I was just saying.
[Guest] 所以他们想让黎巴嫩政府来做这件事。但当然，黎巴嫩政府根本没有这个能力。
So they want the Lebanese government to do it. But of course, the Lebanese government is in no position.
[Guest] 去解除 Hezbollah 的武装。很多人认为，最终结果会是一场内战，一边是 Hezbollah，另一边是黎巴嫩政府。而这会对以色列有利。
to disarm Hezbollah. And many people think that the end result will be a civil war involving Hezbollah on one side and the Lebanese government on the other side. And this will be good for Israel.
[Host] 好吧，我得先稍微换个话题。有位聊天室观众发来留言，我就不说这个人的邮箱地址了。John 是我亲爱的爷爷。
Well, I have to change the topic for just a minute. One of the chatters writes in, I won't tell you what the person's email address is. John is my dear grandpa.
[Host] 所以你的一位孙辈现在正在看我们呢，Mayor Shommer 教授，这真让人开心。我一看到这个就特别兴奋。
So one of your grandchildren is watching us now, Professor Mayor Shommer, and it's a delight. It just excited me to see that.
[Guest] 我希望我的这个孙辈，不管是孙子还是孙女。
I hope my grandchild, whoever he or she is.
[Host] 我不想让这个人尴尬，不过等我们下播之后，我会把这个人的邮箱名告诉你。我的意思是，Trump 现在真的已经没有退路了，对吧？
I don't want to embarrass the person, but I will give you the email moniker of this person when we're off air. I mean, Trump really has no out anymore, does he?
[Guest] 他没有什么好的退路。我的意思是，他基本上可以向伊朗的要求让步，但那样他会在 Israel 和美国的游说集团那里付出极其惨重的代价。我对这个判断的看法是这样的。对
He does not have a good out. I mean, he could basically cave in to the Iranian demands, but he would pay an awful price from Israel and from the lobby in the United States. My view on this judge is that. For
[Guest] Trump 来说，要让步，必须发生的情况是：经济、国际经济、世界经济都得处在快要坠崖的边缘。全球得出现足够大的损害，才能
Trump to cave. What has to happen here is that the economy, the international economy, the world economy has to be on the verge of going off the precipice. There has to be enough damage around the world to
[Guest] 让 Trump 总统干脆对 Israelis 说，够了，不能再这样下去了。我们必须把这件事叫停。这也是为什么我一直认为，从 Iran 的角度看，这场战争拖得越久越有利。
cause President Trump to simply say to the Israelis, enough is enough. We have to shut this down. And this is why I've long argued that from Iran's point of view, the longer this war goes on, the better.
[Guest] 我觉得 Iranians 其实去 Islamabad 是个愚蠢的决定。如果是我替他们下这盘棋，我就不会去 Islamabad。我会让战争继续打下去，因为当时主动权在他们手里。而且战争拖得越久，
I think the Iranians were actually foolish to go to Islamabad. If I had been playing their hand, I would not have gone to Islamabad. I would have just kept the war going because they were in the driver's seat. And the longer the war goes on.
[Guest] 他们的筹码就越多。我认为，到了某个时候，如果战争持续得够久，经济局面也糟到一定程度，Trump 就别无选择，只能和游说集团以及 Israel 正面冲突，逼他们接受某种有实质内容的和平协议。但如果我们始终到不了那个点，这事就只会没完没了地拖下去。
the more leverage they have and I think at some point if the war gets goes on long enough and things get bad enough economically Trump will then have no choice but to clash with the lobby and with Israel and force them to accept some sort of meaningful peace agreement but if we never reach that point this is just going to go on and on
[Host] 嗯。
Hmm
[Host] 嗯，总统现在确实陷入了一个非常棘手的两难处境。这一点毫无疑问。你觉得他明白吗？
Well, the president has a terrible dilemma on his hands. There's no question about that. Do you think he understands?
[Host] 我这个问题问得很蠢。你觉得他明白吗？谁知道他到底明白什么？他身边的人知不知道，Netanyahu 的目标是像 MI6、CIA 和 Israelis 肢解 Syria 那样，把 Iran 也分裂掉？
That's a dumb question on my part. Do you think he understands? Who knows what he understands? Do the people around him know that Netanyahu's goal is to divide Iran the way MI6, CIA, and the Israelis divided Syria?
[Guest] 我相信他们确实知道。我的意思是，我们这里说的是他的顾问，甚至我觉得他本人也是。他们非常清楚自己正处在一个非常危急的局面，我们必须从这场冲突中脱身。你要记住，
I'm sure they do. I mean, they have, we're talking about his advisors here, and I would even imagine him. They understand full well that they are in a desperate situation, that we have to get out of this conflict. You want to remember,
[Guest] 是美国人推动了 Islamabad 那场会面，不是伊朗人。伊朗人只是同意参加这次会面，但真正想促成会面的，是美国人。
it was the Americans who pushed for the Islamabad meeting. It was not the Iranians. The Iranians went along with the meeting, but it was the Americans who wanted the meeting.
[Host] 但那场会面只是做做样子。我的意思是，Vance 根本没有授权。整个过程都被那两个 Zionists 盯着，而且还要向 Netanyahu 汇报，他的那些要求也离谱得很。
But the meeting was just performative. I mean, Vance had no authority. It was monitored by the two Zionists. It was reporting to Netanyahu and his demands were outrageous.
[Guest] 对，但你这里忽略了一点：Trump 夹在两股力量之间。一边是伊朗，以及必须把这件事尽快收掉的现实需要；另一边，是以色列想要摧毁伊朗的意图。所以结果就是，
Yes, but what you're missing here is that Trump is caught between two forces. One are the Iranians and the need to shut this down, and two, the Israeli desire to destroy Iran. So what happens is that
[Guest] Trump 上周二说，我们将会实现停火。这是 4 月 7 日。他说，我们会停火，而且还说，我们实际上会以伊朗提出的 10 点方案为基础展开谈判。
Trump says last Tuesday that we're going to have a ceasefire. This is on April 7th. We're going to have a ceasefire, he says, and he says we're actually going to negotiate on the basis of Iran's 10-point plan.
[Guest] 当时看起来前景很不错。但接下来这一周里发生的事，以及谈判本身实际发生的情况，是以色列和游说集团介入了。然后 Trump 就退缩了。
And this looks very promising at the moment. But then what happens over the course of the week and what actually happens in the negotiations itself is that the Israelis and the lobby weighs in. And Trump backs off.
[Guest] 于是，他没有按照伊朗摆上桌面的那份 10 点方案，在 Islamabad 和伊朗人谈判；相反，和他自己之前说的完全不同，他转而基于另一套方案谈，
And instead of negotiating with the Iranians in Islamabad on the basis of the 10-point plan that the Iranians had put on the table, he negotiates, contrary to what he said he was going to do,
[Guest] 也就是美国更早提出的 15 点方案，而这份方案里包含了以色列想要的所有那些最强硬、最极限的要求。所以你看到的是，最终我们采纳了以色列的立场，而这也成了谈判的基础。
on the basis of the 15-point plan that the Americans had put forward earlier, which includes all the maximalist demands that the Israelis want. So what you see is that ultimately we adopt the Israeli position and that's the basis of the negotiations.
[Guest] 这种事一直都在发生。每次我们表现出一点灵活性，或者有意愿去照顾伊朗方面，以色列和游说集团就会立刻介入，然后我们就采取强硬立场，而这反映的其实是以色列的利益。
And this is what happens all the time. Anytime we show any flexibility, any interest in accommodating the Iranians, the Israelis and the lobby move in and we adopt the hardline position which reflects Israel's interests.
[Host] 而且正如总理 Netanyahu 说得很清楚的那样，我们一路上都在向他汇报。难道你不觉得，当我们向我们的老板、总理 Netanyahu 汇报时，
And as Prime Minister Netanyahu made it clear, we're reporting to him. all along the way. And don't you think that when we report to our boss, Prime Minister Netanyahu,
[Host] 他会非常明确地告诉我们他到底想要什么，而我们就立正听令，照他说的去做。
that he makes it clear to us exactly what he wants and we salute and do what he wants.
[Guest] 而且每次他感觉我们有点不听话了，对伊朗人变得太灵活了，他就会打电话给 President Trump，毫不含糊地告诉他必须重新回到队列里。President Trump 立刻听令，重新归队。
And anytime he senses that we're getting out of line and we're getting too flexible with the Iranians, he calls up President Trump and he tells him in no uncertain terms that he has to get back in line. President Trump salutes, gets back in line.
[Guest] 事情就是这样。
And here we are.
[Host] 我在想，Netanyahu 到底是骗了 Trump，还是威胁了 Trump。
I wonder if Netanyahu tricked Trump or threatened Trump.
[Guest] 很可能两者都有。
It's probably a combination of the two.
[Guest] 我觉得，如果你去看《纽约时报》那篇关于战争前、也就是 2 月 28 日之前，以色列和美国之间谈判或讨论情况的报道，看起来像是以色列人把 Trump 给忽悠了。他们让他相信自己能靠这种神奇手段取胜。
I think that if you look at the New York Times story on what the negotiations or what the discussions looked like between the Israelis and the Americans before the war, before February 28th, it looks like the Israelis bamboozled Trump. They convinced him that they could win this magic.
[Guest] 简直像场神奇的大胜。他们给他兜售了一套说辞，一套货色。而他太轻信了，居然买账了。他没有听顾问的话，也没有追问顾问那些尖锐问题，而这些问题本来可能会让他去反驳摆在台面上的以色列叙事。
magical victory. They sold him a bill. the goods. And he was gullible and he bought it. He didn't listen to his advisors. He didn't ask his advisors tough questions that might have led him to counter the Israeli narrative that was on the table.
[Guest] 所以我觉得他是被忽悠了。但我想说的是，不管当时那些讨论里到底发生了什么，事实是，走到这一步，President Trump 完全明白，Jamie Vance 也完全明白，
So I think he was bamboozled. But the point that I'm making to you is regardless of what happened in those discussions, the fact is, as we move along here, President Trump fully understands Jamie Vance fully understands,
[Guest] Marco Rubio 也完全明白，他们其实几乎别无选择，只能照着以色列和游说集团想要的去做。正如我一直以来所说的，
Marco Rubio fully understands that they really have little choice but to do what the Israelis and what the lobby wants. As I've long argued,
[Guest] 以色列就是套在他们脖子上的一个巨大包袱。如果看到眼下发生的这些事，还需要更多证据，那这个人就真是没救了，因为这个案例已经再明显不过地说明，以色列正在给我们制造巨大的战略和道德问题。
Israel is a huge albatross around their neck. And if anybody needs more proof of that than what's happening here, they're a hopeless cause because it's patently obvious from this case. that Israel is causing us huge strategic and moral problems.
[Host] 伊朗人看得出来美国是在跟着以色列的路线走吗？
Do the Iranians recognize the United States towing the Israeli line?
[Guest] 当然看得出来。我的意思是，你只要听他们怎么说，再看看他们发出来的那些梗图就知道了。到了现在，所有人都明白这一点，连美国国内也是如此。
Absolutely. I mean, all you have to do is listen to them talk and look at all these memes that they're putting out. Everybody understands this at this point in time, even inside the United States.
[Guest] 说实话，我很震惊。2007 年我和 Steve Wall 一起写过一本关于 Israel lobby 的书，2006 年也写过一篇关于这个主题的文章。让我震惊的是，如今大多数美国人都已经意识到，
I'm shocked as someone, you know, who along with Steve Wall wrote this book on the Israel lobby in 2007 and an article on the subject in 2006. I'm shocked at how aware most Americans are today.
[Guest] 游说集团和以色列正在如何以负面的方式影响美国政策。多亏了另类媒体，我们现在终于走到了这一步。
of what the lobby and what Israel are doing to influence U.S. policy in a negative way. We've just reached the point, thanks to the alternative media,
[Guest] 美国有非常非常多的人完全明白正在发生什么。你再看看世界各地，尤其是像 Iran 这样的地方，他们也完全清楚。
that lots and lots of people in the United States fully understand what's happening. And you go around the world, especially to places like Iran, and they understand full well.
[Host] 好，Merchanra 教授，非常感谢你，我亲爱的朋友。你先稍等一下，我会把那个名字告诉你……或者说，把那个说你是他或她亲爱爷爷的人所用的名字告诉你。不过还是一如既往地感谢你的分析。
Well, Professor Merchanra, thank you very much, my dear friend. If you stay with us for a moment, I'll give you the name of... Or the name used by the person who said you are his or her dear grandpa. But thank you, as always, for your analysis.
[Host] 也期待下周再见到你。
And we'll look forward to seeing you next week.
[Guest] 一如既往，是我的荣幸，Judge，我也期待下周见到你。
My pleasure as always, Judge, and I look forward to seeing you next week.
[Host] 谢谢。今天上午 10 点接下来是 Aaron Mate，今天下午 2 点是 Matt Ho，今天下午 3 点是 Colonel Karen Kratkowski。这里是 Judge Napolitano 的 Judging Freedom。
Thank you. Coming up at 10 o'clock this morning, Aaron Mate at two this afternoon, Matt Ho at three this afternoon, Colonel Karen Kratkowski, Judge Napolitano for Judging Freedom.